艾玛去哪了 艾玛
-Where's Emma? Emma?!
艾玛 艾玛
Emma! Emma!
艾玛 你在哪里 亲爱的 艾玛
Emma, where are you, honey?  Emma?
艾玛
Emma?
上帝  我天
Oh God. Oh my God.
你还好吗 哦 上帝
Are you okay?  Oh God.
好了 没事了
Okay. Okay.
哦  谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我看到了一个可怕的男人
I saw a scary man.
既不是命运也不是现实
Neither fate nor society
允许弗朗西斯?穆里根
put Francis Mulligan  in the house
就在15日晚上 闯入凯莱?米切尔的家
of Gloria Mitchell  on the night of the 15th.
既不是命运也不是现实
Neither fate nor society
叫他把她绑起来  用枪指着她
told him to tie her up,  shove a gun in her face
窃取她的财物
and steal her belongings.
那是他自己的选择
That was his choice.
辩方还会站在被告一方么
The defense would have you  walk in his client's shoes.
嗯  我会
Well, I have.
我来自里佛岱尔
I'm from Riverdale.
这是一个craphole
It's a craphole.
没人说它不是  可...
Nobody's saying  it's not, but...
我就是来自那里 不是我是谁
that's where I'm from.  It's not who I am.
他不是受害者
He is not the victim here.
所以 如果你们要站在任何一方...
So if you are gonna put yourself in anyone's shoes...
请...
put yourself...
站在凯莱?米切尔一方
in Gloria Mitchell's.
谢谢
Thank you.
陪审团现在休会 稍后宣判
The jury will now adjourn  to deliberate a verdict.
尼斯来了 看着你呢 前五排
Nice close.  Straight to your top five.
-你喜欢这样 -是的 我做到了
-You like that? -Yeah, I did.
"不是我是谁 " 这句非常经典
"Not who I am."  That was very cute.
-我得走了  -米奇 陪审团刚刚离开
-I gotta go.  -Mitch, the jury only just left.
有罪 五年 两年后假释
Guilty, five years, parole after two.
-你怎么知道的  -第一 法官被我的
-How do you know that?  -One, the judge is soft
有教养的论述所感化 而且没人中枪
on the educationally-challenged and nobody got shot.
第二呢
And two?
我不会输的
I don't lose.
嗯 就算那么回事吧
Well, that part's true.
-这就是我恨你的原因  -晚上见
-That's why I hate you.  -See you tonight.
-往上看 看着我
-Look up. Look up.
-茄子
-Please.
-再来一张  -不要  别拍了
-One more.  -No. Absolutely not.
-手那么小小的  -我知道
-Look at those tiny little hands.  -I know.
我不能相信她看起来如此完美
I can't believe her. Looks so perfect.
她是那么安静
She's so peaceful.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们是幸福的
We're lucky.
对不起 我得走了 今晚得加班
I'm sorry I have to go  to this work thing tonight.
我也希望能在这里陪你
I wish I could  stay here with you.
-扶我下  -小心 这很滑
-Help me.  -Careful, it's slippery.
伙计们 明天见 谢谢你们的酒
Guys.  Tomorrow, thank you.
晚安  伙计们
-Good night, boys.
我他妈的讨厌龙舌兰酒
I fucking hate Tequila!
每个人都讨厌龙舌兰酒  都这么想的
Everybody hates Tequila.  That's the idea.
嗯  我 -我不知道怎么就
Well, I-I didn't know what to get
成为拥有这一切的人  所以
-the man who has everything, so-
这家伙有个好工作  漂亮的小宝宝...
He's got a career, a beautiful little baby...
-哦 我的小亲亲  -...性感的妻子
-Oh, my little baby.  -...a sexy wife.
-当心  -又打击我 -
-Careful.-And then it hits me-
我只能借酒消愁
I'm gonna get the man a Tequila hangover.
米奇 明早见
So, Mitch, tomorrow morning,
你会醒来的 我的朋友
you are gonna wake up  complete, my friend.
是的
That's right.
-谢谢你 谢谢  -我帮过
-Thank you. Thank you.  -I helped.
没问题
Complete.
你一个人回家 没事吧
You okay getting home?
是啊 我打辆车
Yeah. Gonna get a-
-出租车  -好吧
-gonna get a cab.  -All right.
-哦
-Oh.
-喂  -这里是对方付费电话
-Hello?  -This is a collect call
来自协和监狱的一个犯人
from an inmate at Concord penitentiary.
-要接受此呼叫  请按1  -
-To accept this call, press 1.
-没事吧  -没事
-Everything okay?  -Yeah.
是啊  唉  明天见
Yeah.Ugh.See you tomorrow.
听着 半夜你要是酒劲上来
Listen, when you throw up in the middle of the night,
-呕吐时远离宝宝  -知道  我会的
-aim away from your baby.  -Yeah, I will.
-要吐时远离宝宝  -远离宝宝
-Aim away from the baby.  -Away from the baby.
我答应
I promise.
不要在吐在孩子身上 米奇
Don't puke on  your child, Mitch.
-我不会的  -明天见
-I won't puke on my child. -Until tomorrow.
明天见
Tomorrow.
别迟到
Don't be late!
城内的出租车
Inner-City taxi.
-嘿
-Hey!
-城内的出租车 喂
-Inner-City taxi. Hello?
要我帮你们么
Can I help you guys?
他妈的想干什么
What the fuck?
哦  他妈的
Oh, fuck it.
混蛋
Fuck.
什么情况
What the fuck?
哦  天
Oh no.
哦  他妈的 哦
Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
哦  对不起  我不是故意的
Oh, I'm so sorry.  I'm so sorry.
哦  妈的  我很抱歉
Oh fuck.  I'm so sorry.
-哦  妈的
-Oh shit.
嘿  我会叫救护车的
Hey, I'll get an ambulance.
哦  他妈的  哦  混蛋
Oh fuck.  Oh fuck.
先盖上
Take this.
没关系 我会求救的
It's okay. I'm gonna get help.
我这就去叫辆救护车 没事吧 坚持住
I'm gonna get an ambulance, all right? Hold in there.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
嘿 就两分钟  我保证
Hey. Two minutes.  I promise.
-不要丢下我  -我只是去叫救护车
-Don't leave me.  -Just gonna call an ambulance.
两分钟内我会回来的
I'll be back in two minutes.
这是911 你有什么紧急情况
911, what's your emergency?
我需要一辆救护车  一位男士被车撞了
I need an ambulance.  A guy's been hit by a car.
-现在什么位置 先生  -呃  基勒
-What's the location, sir?  -Uh, Keeler.
-基勒和第26街之间  -你叫什么名字  先生
-Keeler and 26th.  -What's your name, sir?
请抓紧时间 快点 他受了重伤
Please just hurry. Hurry, he's hurt real bad.
先生
Sir.
救护车已经在路上了
The ambulance is coming.
-不要离开我  -我得走了 我不能留在这
-Don't leave me.  -I have to go. I can't stay.
我不能留下来 你会没事的
I can't stay.  You'll be fine.
我保证 我保证 对不起
I promise. I promise.  I'm sorry.
-不要丢下我  -我得走了
-Please. No.  -I have to go.
-救救我  -不要 救救我
-Please.  -Please. Please.
他妈的 他妈的
Fuck. Fuck.
救护车就要来了 明白吗
An ambulance is coming, okay?
好吧
Okay?
不要离开我 不要
Don't leave me, please.
-爸爸在这 嘿  亲  -嘿
-There's daddy. Hey, lover.  -Hey.
你在干什么
What on earth are you doing up?
-没有睡好  -宿醉
-I didn't sleep great.  -Hangover?
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么样
How are you?
还好吧  小家伙每一  二个小时就要吃
Well, apparently they wake up every  two hours and they demand food.
-谁知道 -我能做什么
-Who knew?  -Can I help?
是的 你可以修修车库门 快把我逼疯了
Yes,you could fix the garage doors.They're driving me crazy.
抢购一些尿布
Just gonna grab some diapers.
-米奇  -嗯
-Mitch. -Uh-huh.
有什么想告诉我
Something you wanna tell me?
什么
What?
昨晚
About last night?
-什么 -车子么
-What?  -And the car?
瑞...
Rach...
呃...
uh...
车子怎么停在车库里
And why it's parked  in the garage?
你开车回家吗
Did you drive home?
是啊
Yeah.
-你答应坐出租车  -我知道了
-You promised to take a cab. -I know.
不 我的意思是 你疯了吗
No, I mean-What, are you crazy?
因为如果你得到一个D.U.I.(类似酒驾)
'Cause if you get a D.U.I.,
那么你要和D.A.办公室说再见
then you can kiss  the D.A.'s office goodbye.
我知道了 我知道 我很抱歉
I know. I know, I'm sorry.
我不应该  不会再这样了
I shouldn't have. I won't do it again.
米奇 我是认真的 你是个父亲了 好吗
Mitch, I am serious.  You're a father now, okay?
你要抓住机会
You can't afford  to take chances.
我知道了 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
看到了吗 你看 即使艾拉同意
See?  Look, even Ella agrees.
艾拉
Ella?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
嗯  嗯  不要改变话题
Mm-hmm.  Don't change the topic.
我不知道怎么办  如果我失去了你们
I don't know what I'd do  if I lost you guys.
嗯 来爸爸这 我来带她 你去睡觉
Mmm. Here, let me take her.You go to bed.
去休息会吧
Go get some rest.
去爸爸那里了
There you go. Thanks.
就一个小时
Just an hour.
-嘿  -你还好吗
-Hey. -You okay?
是啊  你可以打电话给
Yeah.  Could you call around
周边的医院和诊所么
the local hospitals  and clinics?
我试图追查一个年轻人
I'm trying to track down  a young man who was involved
昨晚午夜前后交通事故
in a hit-and-run accident  last night around midnight.
-与什么案子有关  -只要告诉我你发现了什么就行
-What case is it connected to?  -Just let me know what you find.
拜托
Thanks.
-早上好  警官  -早上好
-Morning, officers.  -Good morning.
-好 这边请  -谢谢
-Good. This way.  -Thanks.
本台记者在警局前发回有关
I'm down here in  front of the police department
一名当地年轻人惨死于一场交通意外的报道
with the story of the tragic  death of this local young man.
昨晚一场似乎普通的交通意外
What started out as a routine  traffic stop last night
演变成可怕的谋杀案的调查
has turned into a gruesome  murder investigation
当警员截停了这辆面包车时
when police officers  stopped this van
就是我身后被警方扣押的车辆
parked behind me  in the police impound
尾灯已经破碎
for nothing more than  a burnt-out taillight.
警员发现车后门附近鲜血淋漓
When they saw blood dripping  from the rear door,
要求司机打开面包车
they demanded  the driver open the van
于是发现了阿克曼的尸体
and it was then they discovered  the body of Cecil Ackerman,
这是一名来自内珀维尔的24岁假释犯
a 24-year-old parolee  from Naperville.
请不要
Please don't.
司机声称他发现了阿克曼
The driver claims  he found Ackerman
躺在路上 表面上看是肇事逃逸
dying in the road  from an apparent hit-and-run
随后设法送他去医院
and was merely trying  to get him to the hospital.
这是杰夫?富兰克林从现场发来的报道
This is Jeff Franklin,  reporting live from the scene.
嘿 律师先生
Hey, counselor.
谢谢
Thanks.
在吗
Yeah?
-加隆侦探  -是
-Detective Kanon?  -Yeah.
"committed"里有几个"T "
How many "T"s in "committed"?
-两个  -该死的文书工作
-Two. -Fucking paperwork.
你来得真是快
You got here fast.
是啊
Yeah.
你说你对阿克曼谋杀有兴趣
You said you were interested  in the Ackerman murder?
是的
Yes, I am.
D.A.安排你来处理吗
D.A. assigned just you?
算是吧  只是预审
Well, it's just  a provisional inquiry.
跟我来
Walk with me.
犯罪嫌疑人名叫  克林顿?戴维斯
Suspect's name is  Clinton Davis.
55岁  汽车修理工
55; Car mechanic;
袭击罪前科 没有做案时间
couple of assault charges, nothing he did time for;
没有亲人 妻女被谋杀
no relatives; Wife and daughter were murdered
死于几年前一个家庭的入侵案件
in a home invasion a few years back.
律师已经来了
Priest was in here already,
说什么他是一个好人  从来没有伤害过一只苍蝇
saying what a good guy he is,  how he'd never hurt a fly,
-等等  -他们说的新闻
-et cetera.  -They said on the news
他在路上发现了塞西尔?阿克曼
that he found Cecil  Ackerman in the road.
是的  我们就在那里
Yeah, we've been there.
现场没有汽车破碎零件  没血迹
No broken car parts,  no blood that we could see.
是的 雪整夜在下 所以...
Yeah, but the snow thawed overnight, so...
我们已经在戴维斯的衣服找到了阿克曼的血液和头发
we've got Ackerman's blood and  hair all over Davis's clothes.
在他的面包车的后面 我们找到了沾血的工具和塑料片
We've got the bloody tools and the  plastic sheets in the back of his van.
我们有足够的证据起诉他
We've got enough to charge him.
你们需要决定  是否足以定罪
You guys need to decide  if it's enough to convict.
-他看起来吓坏了  -应该是
-He looks terrified. -He should be.
20岁生命在他眼前就此消失
He's staring down 20 to life  for this one alone.
他一个人么
This one
我通过数据库查了一些关键字
I ran some keywords through the database.
标记了一系列谋杀
It flagged a string of unsolved homicides.
你觉得这家伙的是个连环杀手
You think this guy's  a serial killer?
你甚至不知道 他杀死了这个家伙
You don't even know that he killed this guy.
告诉你老板  我们会尽一切力量送他上法庭
Tell your boss we'll send him  everything we got.
-米奇  -我有一个请求  先生
-Mitch.  -I have a request, sir.
谢谢 嘿
Thanks. Hey.
米奇Brockden  D.A.的办公室
Mitch Brockden,  D.A.'s office.
我的搭档斯图尔特?威尔逊
My associate Stuart Wilson.
特里?罗伯茨  公共辩护人办公室
Terry Roberts, public  defender's office.
我的名片
There you go.
戴维斯先生 我们要问你几个问题
Mr. Davis, we're going  to ask you a few questions
关于4日晚
about the night of the 4th.
如果你能回答  尽可能准确回答
If you can answer as accurately as possible-
你会是我的检控官
You're gonna be my prosecutor?
呃  如果按正常程序
Uh, if this goes to trial,
那么 是的  我就是
then yes, I am.
我什么都没有做  我是无辜的
I didn't do anything.I'm innocent.
你没有什么就不用担心
Then you've got nothing to worry about.
好吧  戴维斯先生
Okay, Mr. Davis,
我们开始  告诉我们当晚早些时候
let's start with you telling us where you were
你在哪里
earlier that evening.
下班以后  我去了某个团体
Left work, went to group,
然后开车去兜风
went for a drive.
什么团体
Group?
是啊  我在一些互助团体帮忙
Yeah, I help out at some support groups.
-开车去了哪  -只是去我想去的地方
-And the drive?  -Just something I do.
这不违法吧 对不对
It's not against  the law, right?
我的意思是 难道你们晚上不出去或者开车周边转转
I mean, don't you ever go out and drive around at night?
恕我直言 这是题外话
Due respect, I think that's beside the point.
我不喜欢总呆在家里
I don't like to spend too much time at home.
这会唤起我许多回忆
It brings back memories-
我的妻子和孩子
My wife and child.
嗯  我懂
Uh, yes.
我听说过关于你家人的事
I heard what happened  to your family.
我 我很抱歉
I'm-I'm sorry.
伊曼纽尔?费莱 枪杀的第二天晚上
Emanuel fryer. Gunned down the next night
袭击了另外的家庭
attacking someone else's family.
关于受害者我们还知道些什么
What do we know  about the victim?
塞西尔?阿克曼  登记在案的性犯罪者和
Cecil Ackerman-registered sex offender;
儿童性侵 两项罪名 入狱二年
two counts of child sex abuse; Did two years inside;
三个月前假释
was only out on parole three months.
所以是一个真正混混
So a real loss to society.
到目前为止 他和戴维斯之间没找到联系
So far there's no connection between him and Davis.
-凶手用的什么凶器  -武器
-What about the murder weapon?  -Weapons.
死因法医也不能确定
The coroner couldn't be exact,
但他认为这些伤口可能是同一作案工具造成
but he suggested these  wounds could be consistent
用的某一种工具或者机器零件
with the type of tools and machine parts
在戴维斯的面包车后备箱里找到
found in the back of Davis's van.
-确定  -是的 他们还发现
-Could be?  -Well, they also found
可见的油污和伤口里的沙子
significant amounts of oil and grit in the wounds,
这证实了戴维斯的肇事逃逸事实
which corroborates Davis's hit-and-run story.
事实上  维克的D.N.A.和血液
True, but the Vic's  D.N.A. And blood were
遍布戴维斯的衣服 他的面包车里也有
all over Davis's clothes, inside his van.
就是那辆 他把阿克曼抬入的面包车
Which could've got there when he lifted Ackerman into his van.
是啊  或许他杀害了他  戴维斯就有两项罪名
Yeah, or when he murdered him. Davis has two counts
暴力攻击 而他的家人
-of aggravated assault.  -At a time when his family
在反抗入侵的时候 恰好被谋杀
had just been murdered in a home invasion.
他还没有过这么多停车票
He hasn't had so much as a parking ticket since.
什么困扰着你 米奇
What's bothering you, Mitch?
我看不出动机
I don't see motive.
刚拿到的音频文件
Just got this audio file.
这是复制本
Here's the transcript.
这是个911报警电话  有人报告了事故
It was a 911 call. Somebody called in an accident
20分钟后 也就是戴维斯被捕前
20 minutes before Davis was picked up.
救护车到达事发地点
By the time the ambulance arrived at the location,
现场一个人也没有
there was no one there.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
我们有什么办法找到报案者
Is there any way we can find the caller?
-没有 他用的是公用电话  -你怎么知道的
-No, he used a payphone.  -How do you know that?
动动脑子 他会在录音电话中留下姓名么
If he used his cell, it would have his name, phone records.
很好  这是911电话的潜在漏洞
Okay, 911 call's  potentially damaging,
但它不是决定性的
but it's not conclusive.
如果我们不能找到来电者
And if we can't find  the caller,
辨方也找不到
defense probably can't either.
这可能是在芝加哥任何一人
Could be anyone in Chicago.
米奇  那天晚上你在哪里
Mitch, where were you that evening?
-不  米奇醉得话都说不清了
-No, Mitch couldn't string a sentence together
-那晚怎么了 米奇
-that night, right, Mitch?
-是的 谢谢 斯图  -如果这是肇事逃逸
-Yeah, thanks, Stu.  -If it was a hit-and-run,
那就需要那个肇事者
all it takes is for the guy who hit him
主动承认 否则我们还会陷入僵局
to come forward and confess, and we're dead in the water.
某个人可能这样做 是吧
What's the likelihood of anybody doing that, huh?
我们能找到足够证据来定罪
Do we have enough for a conviction?
戴维斯被发现时 死者就在他的面包车里
Davis was found with a dead man in his van.
我们有大量物证
We have a ton of physical evidence.
没有不在场证明 有暴力犯罪史
No alibi, a documented history of violence
他的公设辩护人太嫩了
and his public defender's still in diapers.
米奇能轻松搞定
Mitch will eat him for breakfast.
先以谋杀罪一项控告他
Charge him, murder one.
是您做的尸检吧  医生
You examined  the body, doctor.
以您的的专业判断
In your professional...  opinion,
死因是什么
what was the cause of death?
颅骨钝力外伤
Blunt force trauma  to the skull.
那又是什么原因造成的创伤
And what caused that trauma?
死者的头骨的后面完全粉碎
The back of the skull was badly crushed,
所以很难缩小作案工具的种类
so it's hard to narrow it down to any one item,
但有些痕迹
but some of the marks seemed consistent
与在嫌疑人的面包车发现的锤子
with a hammer found in the suspect's van.
及覆盖在内饰上油脂和机油似乎是一致的
And the interior was covered  in grease and motor oil,
所以某种在这种环境中暴力的挣扎
so any type of violent  struggle in that environment
可能也引发那些伤口并留下明显痕迹
could've also caused those wounds and left that trace evidence.
你说 "似乎是一致的 "
You said, "seemed consistent."
是的
That's correct.
您报告中提到的创伤
Your report talks of abrasions
润滑脂和机油已浸入伤口
and impact wounds with grease  and motor oil in them.
现在 我敢肯定的说
Now the defense I'm sure is gonna argue that-
那些伤口明显是
those wounds indicate
一辆汽车辗过塞西尔?阿克曼造成
that a car ran over Cecil Ackerman
正如被告的证词所说
as per the defendant's testimony
剩下的只是...
and that the rest is just...
并不支持的证据
a misinterpretation of the evidence.
我问完了 法官大人
No more questions, your honor.
这里是911 您发生了什么紧急情况
911, what's your emergency?
我需要一辆救护车
I need an ambulance.
-一位男士被车撞了  -事发地点在哪  先生
-A guy's been hit by a car.  -What's the location, sir?
呃  基勒  基勒和第26大街拐角
Uh, Keeler. Keeler and 26th.
你叫什么名字  先生
What's your name, sir?
请快点
Please just hurry.
-快点  他受了重伤  -先生
-Hurry, he's hurt real bad.  -Sir.
这是你的证人 布诺克顿先生
It's your witness, Mr. Brockden.
医生  陪审团对你的专业上的问题感到陌生
Doctor, the jury will be unfamiliar  with your field of expertise,
所以我会问一个相当简单的问题
so I'll ask  quite a simple question.
就是法医语言学究竟有多准确
Just how accurate is forensic linguistics?
-非常准确  -但它不是绝对的
-Extremely.  -But it's not perfect?
对科学来说不存在绝对
Perfection doesn't happen in science.
好吧 就算十分之一吧  那么
Okay. On a sliding scale of one to 10 then-
您可以反对  律师先生
you may want to object, counselor.
我反对 证人不在现场
The witness's field  is not on trial here.
这个问题我问完了 法官大人
I'll withdraw the question, your honor.
您刚才说 您认为
You stated earlier that you believe
来电者是真实的
the caller to be genuine?
因此 我假设您的意思
By this I assume you mean
他报告的是一个真实存在的
he was reporting  a real accident.
正确
Correct.
你能这么说  只是...
And you can tell this just by...
凭他的声音就可以断定
hearing his voice?
它其实很复杂  但这是肯定的
It's more complicated than that, but yes.
您可以为我们描述下来电者么
What else can you tell us about the caller?
很难肯定
Hard to be certain
从磁带上的声音判断
from the quality of the tape.
听起来是一个白人男性 可能在30多岁
Sounded like a white male-possibly in his 30s-
来自芝加哥南部
from the South of Chicago,
但他尽力掩饰口音
but he's tried hard to soften the accent,
不象您 律师先生
not unlike yourself,counselor.
您来自哪里 里弗代尔
Now you're from where, Riverdale?
你说 你很难 告诉某些...
When you say it's hard  to tell for certain...
这磁带是不清楚的
that the tape is unclear,
它听起来 是一个白人男性
that it seems to be a white male-
来自底层的种族
The underlying ethnicity
这个很难完全瞒过受过专业训练的耳朵
is hard to fully hide  from trained ears.
-是的 又一个好记录  -嗯
-Yes, it's a good recording.  -Uh-huh.
-好的  谢谢  -谢谢你了
-Okay, thank you.  -Thank you too.
-嘿  -员工会议五点开始
-Hey.  -Staff meeting starts in five.
一个不愿留下姓氏叫吉米的 给您来过电话
Someone named Jimmy called,  wouldn't leave a last name.
说是 他出来了 想要见你
Said to tell you he's out and wants to see you.
留下了联系电话 要发您的手机上
Left a contact number. Do you want  me to get him on the phone for you?
不 不用 谢谢你
No no no, thank you.
闻到了吗
Smell that?
这就是自由的味道
That's the smell of freedom.
嘿  那天我给你家去过电话
Hey, so I called your house the other day,
你知道  找过你的
you know, looking for ya.
你的妻子...
Your wife...
她不知道我是谁  是吗
she doesn't know who I am, does she?
你已经走了很长时间了  吉米
You've been gone a long time, Jimmy.
怎么不告诉她  你有他妈的兄弟
How do you not tell her about your own fucking brother?
同母异父的
Step-brother.
面对现实吧  法律上不承认
And let's face it, legally not even that.
-你想玩什么  -不要他妈的装可爱  吉米
-You wanna play like that.  -Don't be fucking cute with me, Jimmy.
我在仓库工作
I was working at that warehouse
挣钱上法律学校的时候 你他妈在哪
to pay my way through law school when you fucking hit it!
我不是一直在做他妈的配件 不是么
I could've been done as a fucking accessory. Huh?
-让你的工作见鬼去  -是啊 我知道 我他妈真傻
-Bye-bye, career.  -Yeah, I know. I was fucking stupid.
妈的  米奇
Fuck, Mitch.
我的意思是 那个时候是带过很多药回来
I mean, Jesus, I was doing a lot of drugs back then.
我是自私
I was selfish.
我有很多他妈的时间
I've had a lot of fucking time
想想我的生活  想想我是谁
to think about my life, think about who I was.
好吗
Okay?
现在  我让你失望
Now I let you down.
但我不会再让你们失望了
But I will not let you down again.
知道么...
Look...
我毕业时遇到了雷切尔
I met Rachel when I was graduating.
她接受了我的申请  到了D.A.办公室
She processed my application to the D.A.'s office.
自从我的妈妈嫁给你爸
Seeing as my ma never officially married your dad-
是啊 你想通 为什么提我们
yeah, you figured  why mention us, right?
吉米  最好我们不要再有联系
Jimmy, it was best for me not to have ties
案子已经结了 知道吗
to a criminal past, you know?
我曾经撒过谎
Once I'd lied on the forms,
-我不知道  -是啊  我明白了
-I couldn't tell  -yeah, I get it.
我明白了
I understand.
-上帝  -我不再是那个家伙了
-God.  -I'm not that kid anymore.
这是... 河谷
Riverdale, it's...
这是另一种生活
It was another life.
好吧  你真幸运
Well, lucky you.
我只得到一个
I only got the one.
别走
Hey.
喂
Hello?
嘿  布诺克顿先生  我是加隆
Hey, Mr. Brockden. It's Kanon.
加隆警官你好
Detective Kanon.
要我做什么
What can I do for you?
在查点东西
Just checking in.
我们失去了一个或两个支持者
We lost a point or two
因为那个法医语言学家
on that forensic linguist.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊  我知道了 这是  嗯 -
Yeah, I know. It's, umm-
戴维斯不可能是那个打电话的  所以...
it's almost impossible to make  Davis the caller, so...
是么
Right.
这么晚了  侦探
It's kinda late, detective.
是否有您所需要的
Is there something you need?
没有  只是想知道
No, just wanted to know
你在为明天上庭做准备
that you're ready for tomorrow.
-什么意思 -什么什么
-What was that?  -What?
你正在录音
You're recording this?
我为什么要录音
Why would I be recording this?
他们说警察很执着
They say that cops are paranoid.
法庭上见
See you in court.
嘿 她是睡着了
She's asleep. Hey.
嘿
Hey.
你身上有股奶味
You smell like milk.
艾拉又吐奶了
Ella was sick on me, again.
尼斯
Nice.
米奇
Mitch. Hey.
看我
Look at me.
米奇
Mitch.
怎么了
What is it?
有什么事瞒着我
Is there something you're not telling me?
是
Yes.
什么 你就不能...
What?  Can't you just...
告诉我吗
Tell me?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
全体起立
All rise.
请座
Be seated.
会议开始前 法官大人
Before session begins, your honor,
我宁愿去替补席
I would like to approach the bench.
我也不能容忍罗伯茨先生迟到
I will not tolerate tardiness, Mr. Roberts.
对不起  法官大人 我早就来了
I'm sorry, your honor, but there has been
案情有重要的进展
an important development.
我们希望 调用一个新的证据
Defense would like to call a new witness.
我反对 法官大人 控方没有事先告知
Objection, your honor.The prosecution wasn't informed of this.
控方也是昨天深夜才找到的
Defense was unaware of their identity until late last night.
是什么重要证人 罗伯茨先生
What is the relevance of this witness, Mr. Roberts?
他就是给911打电话的人
He's the man who made the 911 call.
-什么 什么情况 -肃静
-What? What?  -Order!
肃静
Order.
-法官大人 -我赞同并允许  布诺克顿
-Your honor--I'm inclined to allow it, Mr. Brockden.
是的  我理解  但如果你能 -
Yes, I understand that,but if you could just-
-布诺克顿先生  -布朗博士的实验室
-Mr. Brockden!  -Dr. Brown's lab
进行了一整夜语音分析  我们找到了一个匹配的
ran a voice analysis overnight and we got a viable match.
这名证人何时能到庭
How soon can defense present this witness?
马上  法官大人 他整个审判
Right away, your honor.  He's been in the courtroom
一直在法庭上
this entire trial.
我只是要说
Can I just please say some-
够了
Enough!
打电话给你的证人
Call your witness.
辩方称...
The defense calls...
-吉米?洛根承认了  -什么
-Jimmy Logan to the stand.  -What?
事件惊喜的出现了转机
In a surprise twist of events,
证人的出面
a witness came forward today
终止对我的当事人
and ended the prosecution's case
克林顿?戴维斯的起诉
against Clinton Davis.
证人看见受害人 塞西尔?阿克曼
The witness saw the victim, Cecil Ackerman,
被一个肇事逃逸的司机撞倒
mowed down by a hit-and-run driver
是一辆红色S.U.V. 任伤者躺在路上不管
in a red S.U.V. And left on the road to die.
随后 他拨打了911
He then called 911.
由此看来克林顿?戴维斯
It seems that Clinton Davis
不是这次事件唯一的好人
was not the only  good samaritan in this trial.
戴维斯先生
Mr. Davis?
我只是想希望你一切顺利
I just wanted to wish you all the best.
是的  这就像你说的
Yeah, it's like you said
如果我是无辜的  一切都会水落石出
if I was innocent, everything would work out.
是的 我说过
Yes, I did.
所以 现在怎么样
So what happens now?
-你回到你的生活  -不  不  不
-You go back to your life.  -No no no,
我的意思是 肇事逃逸者
I mean with the hit-and-run driver,
只要有一个目击证人
the one the witness saw.
也许他就会自首
Maybe he'll turn himself in.
是你 你会吗
Would you?
我他妈的爱你  你他妈的婊子
I fucking love you,  you fucking bitch!
-婊子  -别闹了
-Whore!  -Stop it!
-我他妈的杀了你 -别闹了
-I'll fucking kill you!  -Stop it!
-不  别烦我  -不要这样对我  你个婊子
-No! Leave me alone!  -Don't do this to me, you fucking bitch!
我他妈的真的爱你
I fucking love you!
-嘿  -混蛋 让我走
-Hey!  -Fucking let me go!
我他妈的爱你
I fucking love you!
佩德罗?冈萨雷斯的尸体
The mutilated  body of Pedro Gonzales
今天一大早在芝加哥河银行被发现
was found early this morning on the bank of the Chicago river.
据验尸官报告
According to a source at the coroner's office,
他的头骨的后部被重力击碎
the back of his skull was badly crushed,
凶器可能是一个锤子
possibly by a hammer.
他的家人说  最后一次看见他
His family says the last time anybody saw him alive
是上周六在北国商城
was at the north mall on Saturday.
我通过数据库比对过一些关键字
I ran some keywords through the database.
显示为一起未解杀人案
It flagged a string of unsolved homicides.
我不能呆在这
I can't stay here. Shit!
哦  他妈的 不 不
Oh fuck. No. No.
我看了尸检结果
I looked at the autopsy results.
阿克曼上的伤口  和冈萨雷斯身上找到是相似的
The wounds on Ackerman were similar to those found on Gonzales.
阿克曼案子是一起肇事逃逸  还记得吗
Ackerman was a hit-and-run, remember?
伤口不确定
The wounds were inconclusive.
在法庭上是你自己指出  亲口说出来的
You yourself pointed that out at the trial.
尚无定论 确切的说
Inconclusive, exactly.
要么它是两者兼而有之
What if it was both?
阿克曼跑到路上
What if Ackerman ran into the path of a car
他试图摆脱戴维斯
because he was trying to get away from Davis
是谁折磨他致死
who was in the process of torturing him?
这解释不了现场的混乱
It explains why the forensics was so confusing.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
谢谢你来告诉我这些
Thanks for coming by.
嘿
Hey.
哦  妈的
Oh fuck.
先生......
Yes sir...
哦  妈的
Oh shit.
-是啊 你好  -你拿到照片了
-Yeah, hello.  -You get my photograph?
-你要干什么  -别再盯着我不放
-What do you want?  -Stop following me.
我知道你做了什么
I know what you did.
可警方不是还没来电话
And yet the cops haven't come a'calling.
为什么你认为是我呢  米奇
Why you think that is, Mitch?
如果你知道我是司机
If you knew I was the driver,
为什么你没有把我扯进来  嗯
why didn't you just turn me in, huh?
在警局 我不想拿出我的王牌
I didn't want to play my ace in the police station.
我需要在法庭上用
I needed to go to court.
我得让我的同行们组成的陪审团
I had to get a jury of my peers
看看你的卡  证明我是无辜的
to see your card, find me innocent.
你想要合理怀疑
You wanted double jeopardy.
游戏结束 这是一张免费通行证
Bingo. A free pass.
-但你没有揭穿我  -没有必要
-But you didn't expose me.  -There was no need.
我能看到你有良心危机
I could see you were having a crisis of conscience.
-这是一个混蛋的游戏  -远非如此
-Is this a fucking game to you?  -Far from it.
我不会让你就此逃脱
I won't let you get away with this.
不  你会的
Yeah, you will,
要么我毁了你
or I will ruin you.
那么  谁来保护瑞秋和Ella
Besides, who's gonna protect Rachel and Ella
当你因为肇事逃逸被抓起来  嗯
when you get locked up for hit-and-run, hmm?
你说什么
What did you say?
家庭是相当重的东西  米奇
Family is a precious thing, Mitch.
这是我们的职责  对我们男人来说
It's our job as men
保护家人
to protect 'em.
戴维斯
Davis.
嘿 关上门
Hey. Shut the door.
那不是阿克曼
Is that Ackerman?
新闻上的那家伙
And the guy from the news.
必须找出所有这些人有什么关联
Have to work out  what links all these men.
他是怎么挑选受害者  还有为什么
How he's picking his victims and why.
谁怎么选择
How who's picking them?
克林顿?戴维斯
Clinton Davis.
什么
What?
这些都是未解杀人案
These are  the unsolved homicides
那加隆认为 拘禁戴维斯
that Kanon thinks match Davis's M.O.
拘禁戴维斯
Davis's M.O.?
戴维 戴维斯是无辜的
Dav-Davis was innocent.
肇事逃逸 米奇 打911报警者已经证明了这一点
Hit-and-run, Mitch. 911 caller proved it.
我懂  我觉得没那么简单
Yeah, I wish it were that simple.
这他妈到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
他妈的什么情况  米奇
What the hell is going on, Mitch?
之前你接了戴维斯的案子 几乎让自己丢掉资格
First you blow the Davis case, almost get yourself disbarred
而现在呢 你想证明
and now what? You're trying to prove
这家伙是 该死的波士顿扼杀者
that this guy is the goddamn Boston strangler?
斯图  如果我能解释这一点  我会的
Stu, if I could explain this, I would.
病理学家是凭借什么认定这些工具
With what pathologists think were tools.
类似八个月前
The first took place  eight months
戴维斯全家被折磨时使用的工具
after Davis's family was tortured with similar tools.
看见了吧  我认为他选择了他们
You see, I think he picked 'em.
我觉得他选择了所有的人
I think he picked all of them,
可他妈的他们共同点是什么
but what the fuck  do they all have in common?
你看吧  阿克曼是一个儿童性骚扰者
Well, Ackerman was  a child molester.
其他的人都不是
None of the others were.
嗯  他们都是有犯罪记录
Well, they do all have criminal records.
那么 你认为 这种行为开始于
So you think this behavior started
家人的死亡 对吧 -是的  我想是的
with the death of his family, right?  -Yes, I do.
所以 让我想想那里发生了什么
So remind me-what happened there?
一名男子闯进他们的家
A man broke into their home
不断地折磨
and systematically tortured
屠杀他的妻子和孩子......
and butchered his wife and child...
用了杀这些家伙类似的工具
using similar tools to the ones that killed these guys.
还让戴维斯观看了整个过程
The guy made Davis watch the whole goddamn thing.
然后他切开他的喉咙离开 让他自生自灭
Then he slit his throat and left him for dead.
他活了下来 这是一个奇迹
It was a miracle he survived.
这家伙的名字叫  伊曼纽尔?弗莱
The guy's name was Emanuel Fryer-
职业罪犯
career criminal;
枪杀的第二天晚上  另一家被入侵
gunned down the following night during another home invasion;
最近被假释  等等
recently paroled; Blah blah blah.
入室行凶 哦  妈的
-Broken home oh shit.
什么
What?
冈萨雷斯  最近假释
Gonzales, recently paroled.
费莱  最近假释
Fryer, recently paroled.
阿克曼  也是最近
Ackerman  was recently
所有这些人都是最近他妈的假释犯
all these men are recently fucking paroled.
斯图  你他妈的就是个天才
Stu, you are a goddamn genius!
妈的 我爱你 爱死你了
Shit.I love you. I love you.
好了  你说
Okay, so you're saying
唯一的原因  阿克曼是在大街上
that the only reason Ackerman was in the street
是因为 戴维斯在追杀他
was because Davis was chasing him.
-嗯  -然后你离开后
-Uh-huh.  -And then after you left,
-戴维斯终结了  -完美推断
-Davis finished the job?  -Exactly.
如果我能找到证据  你知道吗
If I could just get proof, you know?
戴维斯无法从阿克曼案子开脱
Davis can't be retried for Ackerman,
但如果我能得到的证据表明  他 -
but if I can get evidence that he-
他杀死了其他那些人
he killed those other guys,
我可以把我们双方的交易
I can cut us both a deal.
你在宣誓说了什么  我就做了什么 -
What you said under oath,  what I did-
你没事吗
You all right there?
-我所做的  它只是消失
-What I did,  it just goes away.
米奇  我在假释中
Mitch, I'm on parole.
我却要闯入一个他妈的家伙的家里
I get busted breaking into some guy's fucking house-
帮个忙吧  我不要你进去  我自己来
come on, I don't want you breaking in. I'll break in.
我只要你跟踪他
I just need for you to tail him,
告诉他什么时候回来就行
let me know when he's coming back.
啊  那么它只是小小协助及教唆犯罪
Ah, it's just a little aiding and abetting then.
诶
Eh.
算了  米奇
Forget it, Mitch.
这样吧 我答应你
Let it go. I'm done.
这混蛋真的闯进入你家
That fucker really break into your house?
是
Yes.
当我们正在睡觉
While we were sleeping.
好吧  他要知道你的旅程
All right,he's gonna know your ride.
你可以借给我辆干净的车子吗
Can you rent me a clean set of wheels?
当然
Of course.
谢谢你  吉米
Thanks, Jimmy.
你知道吗  我的意思是
You know what?  I mean that.
我可能是一个混蛋  但我还是你的哥哥
I may be an asshole, but I'm still your brother.
再见  戴维斯
See you later, Davis.
好吧  伙计  再见
All right, guys.See you later.
晚安
Have a good evening.
-呦  吉米
-Yo, Jimmy.
找到什么了
Got anything  tying him to the victims?
不 还没有
No. Not yet.
貌似他在这里吃饭和睡觉  仅此而已
Looks like he eats and sleeps  here, but that's about it.
其余时间  他都花在自助团体
The rest of the time he spends in self-help groups.
你知道 有时他一个晚上去两次
You know, sometimes he goes to two a night.
哦  他妈的  找到了
Oh fuck. That's it.
这就是挑选的受害者
That's how he picks his victims.
杀死他家人的是一个假释犯
The guy that killed his family was a parolee.
他们都在假释期
They're all parolee meetings.
没人注意到这个家伙煮咖啡
Nobody notices the guy making coffee.
他像墙上的苍蝇挂起
He just hangs around like a fly on the wall,
监听他 担心这个家伙再犯罪
listening for the guy who feels worried about re-offending.
是啊  我一直去
Yeah, I've been to those meetings.
-这些人房间里全这样  -没错
-The room's full of guys like that.  -Exactly.
他妈的
Fuck me.
他保留了假释卡
He kept their parolee cards.
吉米  那是什么
Jimmy, what's that?
呃  我们附近有个水泥工地
Uh, we're near the cement works.
应该是休息时间
Must be coffee break or something.
你知道么 很近的
You know, that's pretty close.
是他回来了吗
Is he coming back?
我不知道 他走进一个旧仓库
I don't know. He went into some old warehouse
又出来拿着什么东西  不知道他去哪了
and came out carrying something.I lost him.
-看着像一些旧工具什么的  -盯好了
-Looked like some old tools or something.  -Get the fuck outta there.
吉米 吉米
Jimmy? Jimmy!
吉米  能听到我说话吗
Jimmy, can you hear me?
吉米 吉米 你在吗
Jimmy?  Jimmy, are you there?
我来了 吉米
I'm coming, Jimmy.
吉米
Jimmy!
-吉米  -啊哈  他妈的
-Jimmy!  -Aah! Fuck!
吉米
Jimmy!
-米奇  -吉米
-Mitch!  -Jimmy!
救我
Help me!
你得救我  米奇
-You gotta help me, Mitch!
救我...米奇
Help... Mitch.
呦  吉米
Yo, Jimmy!
哦  请救我
Oh, please help me!
-吉米  -米奇
-Jimmy!  -Mitch!
米奇
Mitch!
哦  上帝
Oh, Jesus Christ.
杰米
Oh Jimmy.
这是911报警中心 有什么紧急情况
911, what is your emergency?
帮帮我
Help me.
救救我吧  谢谢
Help me, please.
他想杀了我
He's trying to kill me.
-快点  -先生
-Hurry.  -Sir?
先生 谁要杀你
Sir, who is trying to kill you?
先生 先生 你在吗
Sir? Sir, are you there?
先生
Sir?
喂  是啊 我需要一辆救护车
Hello? Yeah, I need an ambulance.
你能听到 -你能听到我吗
Can you hear-can you hear me?
你好
Hello?
是的 我需要一辆救护车
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
-靠  他妈的
-Fuck! Fuck!
-别丢下我  -我要搬动你  好吗
-Stay with me. I'm gonna move you, okay?  -
-好吧  -来吧
-Okay?  -Okay.
好 好 来吧
Okay okay, come on.
来吧 留在我身边
Come on, stay with me!
来吧
Come on!
我们走  伙计
Let's go, men.
嘿
Hey!
-嘿  他需要救护车  -放他下来
-Hey, he needs an ambulance.  -Set him down now!
-哦  他妈的  -把按住
-Oh fuck. -Put him down!
-快点  -放下他
-Do it!  -Put him down now!
-快点  快放下  -操
-Now! Down! Down!  -Fuck.
你他妈的跟我开玩笑 哦 混蛋
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Oh fuck.
快
Go!
-他需要救护车  -好了
-He needs an ambulance!  -Cool it!
吉米  上帝  叫他妈的救护车
Jimmy. Oh God, get him a fucking ambulance!
吉米  躺下 就躺那  兄弟
Jimmy, hang in there. Hang in there, brother.
-坚持住  兄弟  -...会人救你......
-Hang in there, brother.  -...can and will be used against you...
-冷静  -躺在那里
-Calm down.  -Hang in there.
你有权请律师
You have the right to an attorney.
我们已经找到一个受伤的白人男性
We've got an injured white male.
-吉米怎样  -他还在昏迷中...
-How's Jimmy?  -He's in a coma...
......医生说有希望
..but the doctors are hopeful.
你要告诉我你们的关系吗
So you wanna tell me what your relationship is to him?
是的  我们  嗯......
Yeah, we're, um...
是同母异父兄弟
step-brothers.
我们的父母只是未正式结婚
Our parents just never married.
这就是为什么他会在法庭上为你说谎
That's why he'd lie for you in court.
没错
Exactly.
那么 为什么现在这样对他
So why turn on him now?
什么
What?
他勒索你了
Was he blackmailing you?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
不是我干的
I didn't do this.
克林顿?戴维斯干的
Clinton Davis did this.
-用你的锤子  -是的
-Using your hammer?  -Yes.
他闯进我家  偷走了我的工具
He broke into my house, he stole my tools.
你有没有报案
Did you report that?
-没有  -没有
-No.  -No.
锤子有你的指纹
It's only your prints on the hammer.
上帝
Jesus Christ.
我打了911报警电话  上帝做证
I made the 911 call, for Christ's sakes.
我为什么要这么做  如果我是有罪的
Why would I do that if I was guilty?
我真的不知道  米奇
I really don't know, Mitch.
可你之前这么干过
But you did it before.
911  有什么紧急情况
911, what's your emergency?
我需要一辆救护车  一个男士被车撞了
I need an ambulance. A guy's been hit by a car.
在什么位置  先生
What's the location, sir?
呃  基勒
Uh, Keeler.
-这是你  对不对  -是的 是的  是的  是我
-That's you, right?  -Yes yes yes, it's me.
我开车撞了阿克曼  然后走了
I hit Ackerman with my car and I left.
这是错误的 我知道 因为我很害怕
It was wrong.I know that, but I was scared.
我喝了酒 这是一个交通意外
I'd been drinking. It was an accident.
我们找到了这个...
We found this...
就在你的工具箱的底部
in the bottom of your toolbox.
沾满了阿克曼的血迹
It has Ackerman's blood  all over it.
一定是戴维斯故意把它放在那里的
Well, Davis must've  put it there.
我帮助阿克曼时 我的卡掉在了现场
I dropped my cards when I was helping Ackerman.
-我一定是掉了一个  -所有的这些证据...
-I must've missed one.  -All of this...
-直接与你有关  -哦  天
-leads directly to you.  -Oh, Jesus Christ.
好了 听我说  好吗 如果我杀了阿克曼
All right, listen, okay? If I killed Ackerman,
为什么我没有钉死戴维斯
why didn't I crucify Davis in court
法庭上当时我有机会  嗯
when I had the chance, hmm?
他是完美的替罪羊
He was the perfect scapegoat.
好吧  这有一个袋子
Okay, there's a bag.
-有个袋子  -是的
-There's a bag?  -Yes.
戴维斯保留的 所有的受害者的I.D.S
Davis kept the I.D.S  of all his victims.
他针对暴力假释者
He's targeting violent parolees
他认为应该重新定罪
that he thinks will re-offend,
就像杀害他的家人
like the man that killed his family.
-包在哪里  -在他家
-Where's this bag?  -In his house.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
-我去过  -你去过
-I broke in.  -You broke in?
你闯进了他房子里
You broke into his fucking house?
事情严重了  米奇...
Seriously, Mitch...
我怎么知道 不是你把它放在那里
How do I know you didn't put it there?
你知道  我不会再回答任何问题
You know, I don't think I should answer any more questions
直到有律师在场
till I have a lawyer present.
你知道  我想
You know, I think
这真是一个非常好的想法
that's a really good idea.
你的电话 斯图尔特?威尔逊从D.A.的办公室打来的
You've got a call-Stuart Wilson from the D.A.'s office.
斯图  你他妈的去哪了
Stu, where the fuck have you been?
对不起  米奇
I'm sorry, Mitch.
这是他们唯一的让我和你谈谈的方式
This is the only way they'd let me talk to you.
现在你听我说 你他妈的王八蛋
Now you listen to me, you fucking son of a bitch.
我会找到你  我会来的  我会取你性命
I will find you, I will come for you and I will take your life.
-你听到了么 戴维斯  -哦  听着呢
-You hear me, Davis?  -Oh, listen to you.
当你打Ackerman的时候  你的决心在哪
Where was all that backbone  when you hit Ackerman, huh?
如果你曾表露过决心
If you'd showed it then,
你就会一直等到救护车到来 这样他也不会死
you would've waited for the ambulance and he'd be alive.
当然 他还是会不被约束的
Course, he'd still be free
-到处去伤害孩子们...
-to go around hurting small children...
-...这也是我带走他时他正在做的
-...which he was about  to do when I took him.
你其实是知道的 对吧
You do know that, right?
如果你让他好好的一个人呆着
If you'd let well enough alone,
我们永远也不会来到这个地方 米奇
we never would've come to this place, Mitch.
你想干什么
What do you want?
你可以毁了我的生活
You could've ruined my life
或毁了你的
or ruined yours,
但你却发现 第三个选项
but yet you found a third option.
一是帮助我们两个
One that helped us both.
有没有他妈的第三个选项
There is no fucking third option here.
是啊  有
Yeah, there is.
如果在他们拘禁你的同时
What if another murder happened  with the same M.O.
发生了另一起相同手法的谋杀怎么办
While they have you  in custody, hmm?
走向清白的道路是漫长的
Go a long way towards shedding light on your innocence
即使是因内疚给出一个合理的怀疑
or even throw a reasonable doubt on your guilt.
你说什么  你在说什么
What are you-what are you talking about,
-另一起凶杀案么  -问题是
-another murder?  -The problem is
你不知道我的痛
you don't know my pain
还有我的空虚
or my emptiness.
可现在你要知道为什么是我
But now you're going  to know what it is to be me.
戴维斯 戴维斯 是什么...
Davis?  Davis, what...?
你在哪里 戴维斯 嗯
Where are you, Davis? Huh?
我现在得走了 米奇
I have to go now, Mitch.
戴维斯
Davis!
嘿  掉线了 嘿
Hey! Is the line cut? Hey!
我要打个电话  我要往外打个电话
I need a line. I need an outside line.
-戴维斯要杀我妻子  -停
-Davis is going to kill my wife! -Stop!
-嘿  -那混蛋会杀了我的妻子
-Hey! -He's gonna kill my fucking wife.
-Brockden夫人  -我是
-Mrs. Brockden?  -Yes.
我是加隆警官  我不想打扰你
I'm Detective Kanon. I hate to bother you
在这痛苦的时刻  但我想问你几个
at this ungodly hour, but I'd like to ask you
有关你丈夫的问题...
some questions about your husband...
......如果可以的话
...if it's  all right with you.
没事  当然 -我
No, not at all. Of co-I'm-
就一会儿
just one minute.
犯罪嫌疑人 大约55  ...
Suspect is approximately 5'5"...
你知道  我打了一天的电话  我 -
You know, I've been calling all day and I-
我希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
嘿  警官  刚刚见了一个客户
Hey, officer. Just finished up with a client.
你能告诉我 为什么逮捕我丈夫
Can you tell me what you've arrested my husband for?
-谋杀  -什么
-Murder.  -What?!
我的意思是 这是疯了 米奇
That-I mean,that's insane. Mitch
我知道 我知道  -这是疯了
I know.I know it  -it's crazy.
我个人相信他是无罪的
And I personally don't believe he's guilty at all,
但我只需要问你几个问题 以便澄清
but I just need to ask you some questions to clear-
你能给我倒杯水吗
Could you get me a glass of water, please?
嗯 是的 当然可以
Um, yeah, sure.
晚安 律师先生
Good night,counselor.
小心开车
Drive safe.
你说的没错
There you go.
你看 我只是不明白
Look, I just don't understand.
如果你知道他没有那么做 你为什么还拘押着他
If you know that he didn't do it, then why are you still holding him?
其他侦探对他的事情也有不解之处
Some of the other detectives are having a problem with his story.
就像我说的 我们曾经谈过
But like I said, once we have our conversation,
我确定可以澄清一切
I'm sure we can clear that all up.
-他接了个电话就疯了  -谁打来的
-He got a phone call and he went crazy.  -Who called?
威尔逊什么的 好像是从D.A.的办公室
Wilson or something from the D.A.'s office.
他咆哮着拨打了另一个电话
He was ranting about making another call,
有人说是要杀他的妻子 戴维斯
said someone was gonna kill his wife. Davis.
什么情况
What the hell's going on in here?
-刚刚是你打电话给米奇  -不是
-Did you just call Mitch?  -No.
申请支援 去Brockden家 快
Get a unit over to Brockden's house now.
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel! Rach!
哦  有人么 谁来救救我
Oh, somebody! Somebody help me!
-起来  -不  你为什么要这么做
-Get up. -No! Why are you doing this?
-起来  -不
-Get up.  -No!
请  不要杀我
Please, don't kill me.
-不要  -不要伤害她
-No. -Don't hurt her!
米奇 米奇
Mitch. Mitch.
枪扔过来
Toss the gun over here.
快点
Do it.
雷切尔 我要你弯腰
Now, Rachel, I want you to bend down
拿着枪管 捡起来
take that gun by the barrel
交给我
and pass it to me.
不管你想怎样 克林顿 结束吧
Whatever you're thinking of doing, Clinton, don't do it.
别说没用的 是你自己搞砸了
Well, it looks like you just fucked up
我们合理的疑问 米奇
our reasonable doubt here, Mitch.
你的家庭发生了什么可怕的事
What happened to your family was terrible.
这样做  改变不了这一切
Doing this, it's-it's not gonna change that.
我那是在保护别人的家人不再受伤害
I was protecting other people's families.
现在谁在保护你的家人 米奇
Who's gonna  protect yours now, Mitch?
你么
You?
现在你懂了吗 会有人救你吗
You understand now? Do you get it?
是啊  我懂了
Yeah, I get it.
我知道你的妻子和孩子
I get that you watched your wife and child
被折磨致死  而你什么也没做
tortured to death and you did nothing.
你就是个他妈的懦夫
I get that you're a fucking coward.
没话说了吧
You froze.
你关心自己胜过自己的亲骨肉
You cared more about saving yourself than your own flesh and blood.
-米奇  别说了  -你认为找出
-Mitch, please don't  -You think if you take out
尽可能多的假释犯...  -闭嘴
-as many parolees as possible...  -Shut up.
你的家人就不会死了
...you'll make what happened to your family go away.
-别说了  -你知道 如果你还是一个男人...
-Please. -You know, if you were a man...
一个真正的男人 你应该先死
a real man, you would've died first.
我已经死过了
I thought I was dead.
四肢被绑着  喉咙被切开
I was hog-tied  with my throat cut
我是那么的不幸
but I wasn't so lucky.
亲眼看着家人折磨死去
I had to watch my loved ones die.
不过 你没有被绑  米奇
You're not tied up though, Mitch.
那么 你要怎么选择
So what are you gonna do, huh?
你愿意先去死
Are you willing to die first?
我愿意
Yes.
是的  我可以
Yes, I am.
我们看看吧
We'll see about that.
哦  米奇  不
Oh! Mitch! No!
你要体验
You need to understand,
看着你爱的人
to see someone you love
流血过多 死在您的眼前 是什么感觉
bleed to death in front of your eyes.
不要 住手
Please. Please don't.
-不要开枪  -乞求是没用的 雷切尔
-Please don't. -Begging won't help, Rachel.
我妻子也乞求过
My wife begged.
这是在浪费时间
It's a waste of time.
-现在.. -不  不要
-Now..-No! No!
很快你就会体验到我的感受了
Now you're gonna see what it's like to be me.
拜托
Please!
感受到我一样的空虚
To feel my emptiness,
一样的痛苦
my pain.
会给你一些从来没有过的东西 米奇
I'm gonna give you something I never had, Mitch.
来证明你可以做的比我更好
Prove you can  do better than I did.
-请  -开枪吧
-Please. -Go ahead.
-拯救...你的家人
-Save... your family.
米奇 不
Mitch, no!
米奇
Mitch!
要我扶你吗
Can I help you with anything?
哦  太可笑了
Oh, you're hysterical.
瑞秋
Rach!
瑞秋 他来了
Rach, he's here.
艾拉给我  打个招呼吧
Give me Ella, then you can say hello.
-我来抱会  -知道了
-Yeah, I got her.  -I know.
-我妻子 蕾切尔  -嘿
-This is my wife Rachel.  -Hey.
我的兄弟吉米
This is my brother Jimmy.
-你好  吉米  -哇  你好
-Hello, Jimmy.  -Wow, hi.
-你还好吗  -比我想的好多了
-How are you?  -Better than I look.
这是...
And this...
-天哦  -这是你的侄女......
-Oh Jesus.  -This is your niece...
艾拉
Ella.
哦  太可爱了 你好  艾拉
Oh my God. Hi, Ella.
艾拉  那是你的叔叔吉米
Ella, that's your Uncle Jimmy.
嘿  艾拉
Hey, Ella.
哦  太可爱了
Oh my God.
哦  米奇
Oh, Mitch.
你给她起个小名
You named her after your ma.
太棒了
Wow.
嗨  你们两家伙别傻站了
Well, I don't know about you guys,
-我都要冻僵了  -是啊
-but I am freezing.  -Yeah.
-吉米 可以请你进来吗  -是啊  好 很荣幸
-Jimmy, wanna come in?  -Yeah, all right. Definitely.
-抱着她没问题吧  -有点紧张
-You okay with her?  -This is terrifying.
你怎么做到这一点
How do you do this?